every time I see her lost in her books
or passionately following her dreams I'm
reminded of a promise I made to myself
to give her every opportunity to SAR her
dream is to be an astronaut and my dream
to make hers come true I've taken steps
to secure her future with a savings plan
but what if life takes an unexpected
turn what if I'm unable to pay future
premiums that's where the ICICI Pro wave
of Premium Rider comes in it's my way of
protecting her dreams the rider comes
with three options Life Health and life
and health the life option means if I'm
not around the future premiums are waved
off yet her policy continues ensuring
her education fund is secure the health
option protects against covered critical
illnesses and accidental disability it
makes sure her dreams are protected
without the burden of paying future
premiums and the life and health option
it covers death accidental disability
and covered critical illnesses ensuring
no matter what life throws at us her
future remains bright with this ICICI
Pro waiver of premium Rider I know I've
done everything to safeguard her future
it's not just a plan it's a father's vow
to his
daughter